If there was a billboard, you could put
a message on, a quote, what might you
put on the billboard?
>> Be the one that takes advice. I don't
give advice because if a person is
asking for advice, typically they're not
the person that really takes the advice
really. It's almost always a waste of
your time. But if you're the one that
genuinely takes advice and it's
ironically me giving you advice to be
the one that takes advice. But if you
can do that, if you can manage that,
then you won't need advice here in 6
months. You'll be the one giving it,
right? So maybe that's what I'd put on
the billboard.
>> So someone sees that, they're like, you
know what? I like the sound of that. I
want to be someone who takes advice. How
might that manifest?
>> They'd have to really pay attention to
the advice that's been given to them.
The world around you is trying to tell
you stuff all the time if you're paying
attention to it. Don't think of the
world as just buildings and people
walking around. You think of it as
education. Truly try to take things from
moments and be open to them. Any serious
philosophy has to be coupled with
openness and curiosity and somebody
willing to let the ideas impact them. I
just think education, advice giving,
people often relegate it to a classroom.
If you strip away all the rules there
and re-territorialize it, education is
constant. It's constantly going on.
That's what I'd add to it.